Eagle Bing looking right daily looking
up the right America before burn when
will this administration ever learn
tariff tantrum economics down war when
the market falling down
B alliances within it's hard to leave
the world when you can't even win
farmers losing billions closing doors
working class doors diplomacy allies put
away
more shade terror tantrum economics down
when the market falling down
alliance within it's hard to leave the
world when you can't even win the world
moved on without build on paper wall
acting dumb but looking foolish cry
before economist
[Music]
the warning history is shown take war of
no winners only get that short-term
thinking long-term pain eod
[Music]
it's hard to leave the world when you
can't even win western leadership in
Fashioned global order rearranged
all because one man's ego couldn't be
contained.
[Music]